Lipsky, David, Papers /4077
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Newspaper Articles, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Related Articles, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Working Paper 941-77 (MIT), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Employment in Perspective: Working Women 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Labor Developments, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Little Brown & Co., 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- A. Greene, Little Brown, 1979-1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Mary E. Beres, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Brock Manuscript Letters, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Brock Manuscript - Orig. (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Brock Manuscript - Orig. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Brock Manuscript Revisions, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Brock Manuscript Revision, cont'd., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Briscoe, Bacharach, Blau & Ferber, Dilts & Paul, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Fottler & Scott, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Harmon & Mayer MS Correspondence, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Harmon & Mayer MS Chapters 8-11 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Stephen, Holoviak, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Arnold M. Howitt, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Mayer & Harmon, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Moag & Vecci, James Portwood, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Marcus H. Sandver, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Marcus H. Sandver, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Patrick Westerkamp, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Kochan & Barocci, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Kochan & Barocci, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Kochan & Barocci, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Kochan & Barocci, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Marcus Sandver, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)